My name is Anthony Maddaloni and I'm going to be talking about photography lighting accessories.
Now photography lighting accessories can run in a whole range of photographic items that you can use.
Mainly using lighting.
One is obviously a flash and the other is actually called a radio slave which I used to like to incorporate in my photography a lot.
Now a radio slave is a type of flash that is triggered by frequencies that get put out by the flash on your camera so if I was photographing an event and I wanted a little bit of a fill flash to lighten up the background as my camera flash went off, that flash would go off in the background too.
That was really one of my favorite lighting accessories to use.
One lighting accessory that you can also use is a sink chord which you can attach to your flash unit so you can hold it off camera.
Now one really cool thing about that is that you can essentially use your flash and you can bounce it off of low ceilings thus not giving such a harsh lighting effect when people use on camera flash.
Those are pretty essential accessories to me.
Another would be like a flash card or a unit that you really can just sort of mount and it diffuses the flash so that it is not as harsh.
Now certain manufacturers make items that you could put on your flash.
It is really nice to buy one they cost about 50 bucks but you could also make them out of certain things.
Sometimes I just use old foam board and I make things out of them like that but those are lighting, flash lighting accessories that you can use in photography.